{
    "subject": "resource/Little_Red_Riding_Hood's_Zombie_BBQ",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:2008_video_games",
    "human_readable": "Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ is about 2008 video games.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8752666115760803,
            "question": "What year were the video games featured in 'Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7766377925872803,
            "question": "Is there a story mode in 'Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.772523820400238,
            "question": "Who developed 'Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6910614967346191,
            "question": "What is the genre of 'Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6830503344535828,
            "question": "Can you describe the gameplay mechanics of 'Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6822806596755981,
            "question": "What platforms was 'Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ' released on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5704695582389832,
            "question": "What is the overall tone or style of 'Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5697091221809387,
            "question": "Are there any unique elements or features in 'Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5237606763839722,
            "question": "What theme does 'Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ' explore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5195314288139343,
            "question": "Did 'Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ' receive positive reviews?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ is about 2008 video games.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3137_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What theme does 'Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ' explore?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3137_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any unique elements or features in 'Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3137_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the overall tone or style of 'Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3137_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3137_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3137_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3137_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3137_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3137_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3137_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3137_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3137_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3137_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3137_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents provide information that supports this triple. Specifically, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3137/re-ranker-msmarco/4.txt mentions that \"Little Red Riding Hood\u2019s Zombie BBQ (NDS)\" was released on October 28, 2008, which is a relevant detail to the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Little Red Riding Hood's Zombie BBQ is about 2008 video games.\" Specifically, multiple sources mention the release date of October 28, 2008, and describe it as a game released in 2008 for the Nintendo DS."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}